RONNY SCHUMM

Senior Blockchain Developer

**** +1 435 621 0239

@ highcrypto098@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A skilled blockchain developer with 7 years of professional experience looking to contribute knowledge in web and blockchain technology to Blockchain ecosystem. Proficient at performing well as working in a group or independently in a fast-paced setting. Deep understanding of distributed ledger, blockchain safety, blockchain design principles, and various blockchain protocols and environments.

EXPERIENCE

06/2020 - 05/2022 •

Senior Blockchain Developer

Location

PayMaya

- To start the research method, I conducted a preliminary customer evaluation and statistics.
- Rest-based applications were created to enhance the user interface with regard to interactivity.
- Using the solidity framework features, optimized the smart contract program and boosted performance by 20%.
- Assisting the chief operating officer with day-to-day operational duties.
- Designed the Blockchain design architecture for the product staff, and determined entry restrictions and safety.

11/2016 - 04/2020

Blockchain Developer

Location

Xendit

- · Built the backend API using Nest.js
- · Integrated Twitter Login based on Auth0 service
- · Worked on various networks including Ethereum, Solana, Polygon
- Developed and deployed 10+ NFT minting/staking platforms
- · Artwork/metadata generation
- · ERC721 development/deployment
- Deploying candy machines for Solana network
- Integrating minting contract with the frontend using web3.js/Anchor
- Configuration of start date and timer
- Presale/whitelist configuration
- Implemented staking/breeding/airdrop with ERC20 tokens and SPL tokens as rewards
- Developed token and DEX platform on Ethereum network
- Extended the DEX platform onto Polygon
- Developed a bridge to cross-operate the token on multiple networks
- Integrated contract using web3.js
- Developed wrapped token and DEX platform using project-serum on Solana network

EDUCATION

08/2012 - 03/2016

Bachelor of Science - Computer Science **Universiti Tenaga Nasional**

Location

LANGUAGES

Enalish Advanced



Malav Native



SKILLS

C++	C++ Algorithm Ne		s Re	eact.js	Rust	Python		Bitcoin Eth		iereum Sol		dity	Solana
Blocko	chain Archite	cture	Api	API Gat	teway	Aws	Axios	Azu	re	Blockch	nain	Boots	strap
Config	guration C	ss3 C	ypress	Digit	talOcean	Dja	ngo	Dynam	odb	Es5	Es6	Eth	ereum
Ethers	s.js Expres	ss.js F	igma	Git	Github	Gitla	ab H	leroku	Jira				